Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files A-E, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files B
    - Brown, Cynthia (Box A-17, Folder 47)
      Also one velox print. One set of 8 prints attached to a photocopied newspaper clipping with paper clip.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, NYC Housing Authority
    - Brown, Cynthia (Box A-17, Folder 48)
    - Brown, Daniel (Box A-17, Folder 49)
    - Brown, Daphne Coleman Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 50)
      Photographer if identified: Ace Photo Studio
    - Brown, Darryl (Box A-17, Folder 51)
    - Brown, Deborah (Box A-17, Folder 52)
    - Deborah Brown (Box A-17, Folder 53)
      Photographer if identified: University of Hartford News Bureau
    - Brown, Della Scott (Box A-17, Folder 54)
    - Brown, Delores (Box A-17, Folder 55)
      Photographer if identified: The Lensman
    - Brown, Denera A. (Box A-17, Folder 56)
    - Brown, Denise (Box A-17, Folder 57)
    - Brown, Dennis (Box A-17, Folder 58)
    - Brown, Derek C. Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 59)
    - Brown, Diane (Box A-17, Folder 60)
    - Brown, Dillard H. (Box A-17, Folder 61)
      Photographer if identified: Protestant Episcopal Church, Public Relations Division
    - Brown, Donald (Box A-17, Folder 62)
    - Brown, Dorothy L. (Box A-17, Folder 63)
    - Brown-Downs (Box A-17, Folder 64)
      Photographer if identified: Diaz & Rogers
    - Brown, Drew "Bundini" (Box A-17, Folder 65)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, United Press International
    - Brown, Drew B. (Box A-17, Folder 66)
    - Brown, Drew H. (Box A-17, Folder 67)
    - Brown, Earl A. (Box A-17, Folder 68)
    - Brown, Early (Box A-17, Folder 69)
    - Brown, Ed (Box A-17, Folder 70)
    - Brown, Ed. Col. (Box A-17, Folder 71)
      Photographer if identified: Ray W. Jones
    - Brown, Edmund (Box A-17, Folder 72)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Gov.) (Box A-17, Folder 73)
    - Brown, Edmund T. (Box A-17, Folder 74)
      Photographer if identified: F. & M. Schaefer Brewin Co.
    - Brown, Edward (Box A-17, Folder 75)
    - Brown, Edward A. (Box A-17, Folder 76)
    - Brown, Edward Jr. (Box A-17, Folder 77)
    - Brown, Edward L. (Box A-17, Folder 78)
    - Brown, Effie Clark Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 79)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Ernie Pile
    - Brown, Elbert (Box A-17, Folder 80)
    - Brown, Elfreida (Box A-17, Folder 81)
    - Brown, Elizabeth (Box A-17, Folder 82)
    - Brown, Ella G. (Box A-17, Folder 83)
    - Brown, Elmer (Box A-17, Folder 84)
    - Brown, Elsie (Box A-17, Folder 85)
    - Brown, Emma (Box A-17, Folder 86)
    - Brown, Ensign Jesse (Box A-17, Folder 87)
      Photographer if identified: Naval Photographic Center
    - Brown, Eric (Dr.) (Box A-17, Folder 88)
    - Brown, Ernest (Box A-17, Folder 89)
      1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    - Brown, Etta Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 90)
      One print has a staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Alex Summers, Alex Hamilton
    - Brown, Eugene (Box A-17, Folder 91)
    - Brown, Eunice I. (Box A-17, Folder 92)
      One print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Parkway Studios, James Gilbert
    - Brown, Eva (Box A-17, Folder 93)
      One print has a staple through the edge.
    - Brown, Evelyn (Box A-17, Folder 94)
    - Brown, Everald (Box A-17, Folder 95)
    - Exa Louis Brown (Box A-17, Folder 96)
    - Brown, Frank (Box A-17, Folder 97)
    - Brown, Frank (Box A-17, Folder 98)
    - Brown, Fred (Box A-17, Folder 99)
    - Brown, Fred (Box A-17, Folder 100)
    - Brown, Freddie L. (Rev. and family) (Box A-17, Folder 101)
    - Brown, Frederick (Box A-17, Folder 102)
    - Brown, G. L. (Bishop) (Box A-17, Folder 103)
      See also Grace L. Brown
    - Brown, G. N. (Rev.) (Box A-17, Folder 104)
    - Brown, Garris (Box A-17, Folder 105)
    - Brown, George (Box A-17, Folder 106)
    - Brown, George (Box A-17, Folder 107)
      1 velox print.
    - Brown, George L. (Box A-17, Folder 108)
    - Brown, George S. (Box A-17, Folder 109)
    - Brown, Gerard (Box A-17, Folder 110)
    - Brown, Ginger (Box A-17, Folder 111)
    - Brown, Grace B. Miss (Box A-17, Folder 112)
      Photographer if identified: Cameron
    - Brown, Grace L. (Box A-17, Folder 113)
      1 print mounted to cardboard, with newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Bunny Photo Studio, L. St. Clair Dummett
    - Brown, Grady C. (Box A-17, Folder 114)
    - Brown, Graham (Box A-17, Folder 115)
    - Brown, Grayson W. (Box A-17, Folder 116)
    - Brown, Gregory Rev. (Box A-17, Folder 117)
    - Brown, Gregory Rev. (Box A-17, Folder 118)
    - Brown, Hampton P. (Box A-17, Folder 119)
    - Brown, Harold (Box A-17, Folder 120)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Mitchell, Wagner International Photos
    - Brown, Harold (Box A-17, Folder 121)
    - Brown, Harold (See George F. McGrath) (Box A-17, Folder 122)
    - Brown, Harriet (Box A-17, Folder 123)
    - Brown, Harry (Box A-17, Folder 124)
    - Brown, Hazel C. (Box A-17, Folder 125)
      Print taped to cardboard.
    - Brown, Helen Butler (Box A-17, Folder 126)
      One print has staple through edge. One print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    - Brown, Henry H. (Box A-17, Folder 127)
    - Brown, Henrietta (Box A-17, Folder 128)
    - Brown, Mrs. Henry (Box A-17, Folder 129)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Bartin?
    - Brown, Herman (Box A-17, Folder 130)
    - Brown, Herman (Box A-17, Folder 131)
      All 3 prints mounted to matte.
    - Brown, Hilton (Box A-17, Folder 132)
    - Brown, Hon. Homer S. (Box A-17, Folder 133)
      One paper stereotype matrix with newspaper clipping attached to verso with staple
    - Brown, Hosea III (Box A-17, Folder 134)
      Photographer if identified: Carol Studios
    - Brown, Howard J. M. D. (Box A-17, Folder 135)
      Photographer if identified: United Hospital Fund
    - Brown, Howard R. Dr. (Box A-17, Folder 136)
      Photographer if identified: New York Times Studio
    - Brown, Irene (Box A-17, Folder 137)
    - Brown, J. Alphonso "Al" (Box A-17, Folder 138)
    - Brown, Rev. J. B. (Box A-17, Folder 139)
    - Brown, James (Box A-17, Folder 140)
      Also 7 velox prints and 2 large halftone prints.
      Photographer if identified: Ralph Garcia, Wagner International, Ideal Photo, Kwame Brathwaite, Cecil Layne
    - Brown, James (Box A-17, Folder 141)
      Also 2 velox prints and 1 large halftone print.
      Photographer if identified: Charal Photo, Bill Moore, Gruen, Frank Cupelli
    - Brown, James (Box A-17, Folder 142)
      Also 2 velox prints and 2 halftone prints.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Relations Publiques, Wagner International,
    - Brown, James (Box A-17, Folder 143)
    - Brown, James (Box A-17, Folder 144)
      Photographer if identified: Edward R. Chew
    - Brown, James (Box A-17, Folder 145)
    - Brown, James Committee for a Harlem High School (Box A-17, Folder 146)
    - Brown, James (Alef) (Box A-17, Folder 147)
    - Brown, James Jr. (Box A-17, Folder 148)
    - Brown, James C. Rev. (Box A-17, Folder 149)
    - Brown, James E. (Box A-17, Folder 150)
    - Brown, James Emanuel (Box A-17, Folder 151)
    - Brown, James N. (Box A-17, Folder 152)
    - Brown, James R. (Box A-17, Folder 153)
    - Brown, Jan (Box A-17, Folder 154)
    - Brown, Janice (See "Miss Homecoming" Shaw University) (Box A-17, Folder 155)
      Print is a mounted color Polaroid. Also one velox print.
    - Jerry Brown (Box A-17, Folder 156)
      Photographer if identified: Donovan Gopie
    - Brown, Jesse (Box A-17, Folder 157)
      One print is stuck to folder.
    - Brown, Jessie L. (Box A-17, Folder 158)
    - Brown, Jewel (Box A-17, Folder 159)
    - Brown, Jill (Box A-17, Folder 160)
    - Brown, Jim (Box A-17, Folder 161)
    - Brown, Jerome A. (Box A-17, Folder 162)
    - Brown, Joanne (Box A-17, Folder 163)
    - Brown, Jocelyn (Box A-17, Folder 164)
    - Brown, Joe (Box A-17, Folder 165)
    - Brown, Joe (in picture with Shavers, Blanche) (Box A-17, Folder 166)
    - Brown, John (Box A-17, Folder 167)
    - Brown, John (R. W.) (Box A-17, Folder 168)
    - Brown, John T. Jr. (Box A-17, Folder 169)
    - Brown, John V. (Box A-17, Folder 170)
      Photographer if identified: Ferlise Photographers
    - Brown, Johnny (Box A-17, Folder 171)
    - Brown, Jonathan (Rev.) (Box A-17, Folder 172)
      Photographer if identified: C. Gill
    - Brown, Joseph (Box A-17, Folder 173)
    - Brown, Joseph (Box A-17, Folder 174)
    - Brown, Josephine (Box A-17, Folder 175)
    - Brown, Josie (Box A-17, Folder 176)
    - Brown, Joyce (Box A-17, Folder 177)
      Photographer if identified: Martha Swope, Zodiac Photographers/Abeles/Friedman
    - Joyce Brown (Box A-17, Folder 178)
    - Brown, Juanita (Box A-17, Folder 179)
    - Brown, Judy (Box A-17, Folder 180)
    - Brown, Julia (Box A-17, Folder 181)
    - Brown, Julienne (Box A-17, Folder 182)
    - Brown, June (Box A-17, Folder 183)
    - Brown, Karen (Box A-17, Folder 184)
    - Brown, Karen Henderson (Box A-17, Folder 185)
    - Brown, Keith (Box A-17, Folder 186)
    - Brown, Kenneth L. (Box A-17, Folder 187)
      Print is mounted to matte.
    - Kevin Brown, Eagle Scout (Box A-17, Folder 188)
      Photographer if identified: David Adderley
    - Brown, LaDonna (Box A-17, Folder 189)
    - Brown, Larry (Box A-17, Folder 190)
      Photographer if identified: Sports Information, East Texas State
    - Brown, Laura (Box A-17, Folder 191)
    - Brown, Lee E. (Box A-17, Folder 192)
    - Brown, Lena T. Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 193)
    - Brown, Lennox (Box A-17, Folder 194)
    - Brown, Leo (Box A-17, Folder 195)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Monroe S. Frederick II
    - Brown, Leola Rev. (Box A-17, Folder 196)
    - Brown, Leon (Box A-17, Folder 197)
    - Brown, Leota (Box A-17, Folder 198)
    - Brown, Leota P. (Box A-17, Folder 199)
      Newspaper clippings taped to verso of 2 prints.
    - Brown, Leslie C. (Box A-17, Folder 200)
    - Brown, Lester B. Dr. (Box A-17, Folder 201)
    - Brown, Lillian (Box A-17, Folder 202)
      Photographer if identified: Whitestone Photo
    - Brown, Linda Leilani (Box A-17, Folder 203)
    - Brown, Lloyd (Box A-17, Folder 204)
    - Brown, Lou (Box A-17, Folder 205)
    - Brown, Louis (Box A-17, Folder 206)
    - Brown, Louis A. (Box A-17, Folder 207)
    - Brown, Louise (Box A-17, Folder 208)
    - Brown, Lula (Box A-17, Folder 209)
    - Brown, Lygia (Box A-17, Folder 210)
    - Brown, Lynn R. (Box A-17, Folder 211)
    - Brown, Madeline (Box A-17, Folder 212)
    - Brown, Mae R. (Box A-17, Folder 213)
    - Brown, Manny (Box A-17, Folder 214)
      Photographer if identified: Hofstra University Football
    - Brown, Marcia (Box A-17, Folder 215)
    - Brown, Marie (Box A-17, Folder 216)
      Photographer if identified: Henry Di Rocco
    - Brown, Marjie (Box A-17, Folder 217)
    - Brown, Marton (Box A-17, Folder 218)
    - Brown, Mary Alice (Box A-17, Folder 219)
    - Brown, Mary B. Mrs./Mary An Brown (Box A-17, Folder 220)
      1 print on matte (Mary Ann Brown). One print has staple through edge.
    - Brown, Mary R. (Box A-17, Folder 221)
      Also one internegative.
    - Brown, Matthew (Box A-17, Folder 222)
    - Brown, Maxine (Box A-17, Folder 223)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, James J. Kriegsmann,
    - Brown, Melvin D. (Box A-17, Folder 224)
    - Melvin-Earl Brown (Box A-17, Folder 225)
    - Brown, Michael (Box A-17, Folder 226)
    - Brown, Mildred (Box A-17, Folder 227)
      Photographer if identified: George Frye, Diana Mara Henry, James Gilbert
    - Dr. Milton Brown (Box A-17, Folder 228)
    - Brown, Minnie (Mrs.) (Box A-17, Folder 229)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Pictorial Enterprise, United Press International
    - Morris Brown Choir (Box A-17, Folder 230)
      Photographer if identified: Hollins Fantastic Photography
    - Brown, Morris Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 231)
    - Brown, Mavis (Box A-17, Folder 232)
    - Mynna R. Brown (Box A-17, Folder 233)
    - Brown, Nathaniel (Box A-17, Folder 234)
    - Brown, Newell C. (Box A-17, Folder 235)
    - Brown, Norman (Box A-17, Folder 236)
    - Brown, Octavius (Mrs.) (Box A-17, Folder 237)
      Photographer if identified: Parkway Photographers
    - Brown, Odie D. Rev. & Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 238)
    - Brown, Oscar Jr. (Box A-17, Folder 239)
      Photographer if identified: Ken Haak, RCA Records, Beuford N.Y., John D. Bunns Jr., Mort Shuman, M Associates,
    - Otha Brown (Box A-17, Folder 240)
    - Brown, Pat (Box A-17, Folder 241)
      Press release stapled to verso of print. Newspaper clippings taped to verso of 2 prints. One print has staple through edge.
    - Brown, Patricia (Box A-17, Folder 242)
      Also one velox print. Staple in one print.
    - Brown, Patrick Mr. & Mrs. (See Corrine Huff) (Box A-17, Folder 243)
    - Patti Brown (Box A-17, Folder 244)
      Photographer if identified: Drake Studios
    - Brown, Paul (Box A-17, Folder 245)
    - Brown, Paul D. (Box A-17, Folder 246)
    - Brown, Paul Ex (Box A-17, Folder 247)
      Photographer if identified: Arthur "Bud" Smith
    - Brown, Pauline R. (Mrs.) (Box A-17, Folder 248)
      One paper stereotype matrix with halftone print attached to verso with staple.
    - Brown, Pearl (Box A-17, Folder 249)
    - Brown, Pearl (Box A-17, Folder 250)
      Also one envelope with 2 4"x5" negatives (stuck together).
      Photographer if identified: Smith
    - Brown, Peggy (Box A-17, Folder 251)
    - Brown, Peggy Dr. (Box A-17, Folder 252)
      Photographer if identified: Lloyd Williams, Harris Photo
    - Brown, Pete (Box A-17, Folder 253)
    - Peter Brown Restaurant (Box A-17, Folder 254)
      Approximately 6 prints stuck together and stuck to folder with paste.
    - Brown, Ponce De Leon (Mr. & Mrs. & Family) (Box A-17, Folder 255)
      Photographer if identified: Platnick Photos
    - Brown, Purcell-Gertrude (Box A-17, Folder 256)
    - Brown, R. Jess (Box A-17, Folder 257)
    - Brown, Rev. R. (Box A-17, Folder 258)
    - Brown, R. D. (Box A-17, Folder 259)
      One print is taped to cardboard.
    - Brown, Rachel W. (Mrs.) (Box A-17, Folder 260)
    - Brown, Radcliff Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 261)
    - Brown, Rap See: Brown, H. Rap (Box A-17, Folder 262)
    - Brown, Raymond (Box A-17, Folder 263)
    - Brown, Raymond E. (Box A-17, Folder 264)
      One print is of Robert A. Tate. Also multiple press releases.
    - Brown, Raymond R. (Box A-17, Folder 265)
    - Brown, Raymond R. (Box A-17, Folder 266)
      2 prints have newspaper clippings taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Harry Kalmus, Ace Creative Photos
    - Brown, Rebecca (Box A-17, Folder 267)
      Print has three staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Sy Hassen Assoc.
    - Brown, Reginald Dr. (Box A-17, Folder 268)
    - Brown, Reginald (Box A-17, Folder 269)
    - Brown, Reginald Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 270)
    - Brown, Richard (Box A-17, Folder 271)
    - Brown, Richard M. (Box A-17, Folder 272)
    - Brown, Robert (Box A-17, Folder 273)
    - Brown, Robert Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-17, Folder 274)
    - Brown, Robert (Box A-17, Folder 275)
    - Brown, Robert (Box A-17, Folder 276)
    - Brown, Robert (Box A-17, Folder 277)
    - Brown, Robert (Box A-17, Folder 278)
    - Brown, Robert (Box A-17, Folder 279)
    - Brown, Robt. (Box A-17, Folder 280)
    - Brown, Robert J. (Box A-17, Folder 281)
    - Brown, Roberta (Box A-17, Folder 282)
    - Brown, Rocky (Box A-17, Folder 283)
    - Brown, Roger (Box A-17, Folder 284)
    - Brown, Roger J. (Commissioner) (Box A-17, Folder 285)
    - Brown, Ron (Box A-17, Folder 286)
    - Brown, Mrs. Ronald (Box A-17, Folder 287)
    - Brown, Rosa (Box A-17, Folder 288)
    - Brown, Rosalie (Box A-17, Folder 289)
    - Brown, Roscoe C. Dr. (Box A-17, Folder 290)
      Also one velox print. 2 prints have staples through border
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Price, Dave Greene, Laima Lurnley, NYC Transit Authority,
    - Brown, Roscoe C. (Box A-17, Folder 291)
    - Brown, Roosevelt (Box A-18, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Roscoe Lee (Box A-18, Folder 2)
      One print has caption taped to verso.
    - Brown, Rose M. L. (Box A-18, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Ross (Box A-18, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Roy (Box A-18, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Monclova Photographers
    - Brown, Roy (Box A-18, Folder 6)
      Print has caption glued to verso.
    - Brown, Roy E. (Rev.) + family (Box A-18, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Luigi
    - Brown, Roy Lee (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-18, Folder 8)
    - Brown, Rudy (Box A-18, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Russell (Box A-18, Folder 10)
      One photocopy with text on verso.
    - Brown, Ruth (Box A-18, Folder 11)
      One print has press release taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Bryan D. Hall, Al Burley, Pictorial Enterprise, James L. Edge, Harris Photo, Bill Moore
    - Brown, Sallie W. (Box A-18, Folder 12)
      Photographer if identified: Snow Studio
    - Brown, Samuel F. Jr. (Box A-18, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Samuel L. (Box A-18, Folder 14)
    - Brown, Sandra (Box A-18, Folder 15)
      Photographer if identified: A.C. Hinton
    - Brown, Sharon (Box A-18, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Shaun D. (Box A-18, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: John Foraste/Brown News Bureau
    - Brown, Sheree (Box A-18, Folder 18)
    - Brown, Sherman (Box A-18, Folder 19)
    - Brown, Shirle (Box A-18, Folder 20)
      Photographer if identified: Johnson
    - Brown, Shirley (Box A-18, Folder 21)
    - Brown, Sidney (Box A-18, Folder 22)
    - Brown, Sitrina A. (Box A-18, Folder 23)
      Photographer if identified: Public Relations Office Livingstone College
    - Brown, Sonny (Box A-18, Folder 24)
    - Brown, Stacey Lynn (Box A-18, Folder 25)
    - Brown, Stephan T. (Box A-18, Folder 26)
    - Brown, Stephen (Box A-18, Folder 27)
    - Brown, Sterling (Box A-18, Folder 28)
      Two prints stuck together. One print has caption glued to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Scurlock, Camera Arts Studio, Boston University Photo Service
    - Brown, Sue A. (Box A-18, Folder 29)
    - Brown Sugar Cosmetics (Box A-18, Folder 30)
    - Brown Sugar Restaurant (Box A-18, Folder 31)
    - Brown, Theodore E. (Box A-18, Folder 32)
    - Brown, Thomas E. (Box A-18, Folder 33)
      Photographer if identified: Kraft Foods
    - Brown, Thomas H. (Prof.) (Box A-18, Folder 34)
      Photographer if identified: George M. West, Bro. David McAdams
    - Brown, Tilmon F. (Box A-18, Folder 35)
    - Brown, Tilmon F. (Box A-18, Folder 36)
    - Brown, Timmy (Box A-18, Folder 37)
    - Brown, Tina (Box A-18, Folder 38)
    - Brown, Tommy (Box A-18, Folder 39)
    - Brown, Tony (Box A-18, Folder 40)
      Two prints are stapled together. Four prints have captions taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, Youngsphoto Productions, Alfred Associates
    - Brown, Tony (Box A-18, Folder 41)
      One print has staple in it. Four prints are stapled together.
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons, Pictorial Enterprise, Public Relations Office American Museum of Natural History, Bert Andrews, Monroe S. Frederick II, Dave Greene
    - Brown, Trevor Calvin (Box A-18, Folder 42)
    - Brown, Tyrone (attorney) (Box A-18, Folder 43)
    - Brown University (Box A-18, Folder 44)
      Print has newspaper clipping attached with paperclip.
    - Brown University school demonstration (Box A-18, Folder 45)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, Office of Sports Informtaion Brown University
    - Brown, Valarie (Box A-18, Folder 46)
    - Brown, Venita (Box A-18, Folder 47)
    - Brown vs. Board of Education (Box A-18, Folder 48)
    - Brown vs. Board of Education (Box A-18, Folder 49)
      A 10-leaf stapled photocopy of a court decision and one newspaper clipping.
    - Brown, Victoria (Box A-18, Folder 50)
    - Brown, Vincent (pvt.) (Box A-18, Folder 51)
    - Brown, Vincent (Rev.) (Box A-18, Folder 52)
    - Brown, Vincent W. (Box A-18, Folder 53)
    - Brown, Vinnie (Box A-18, Folder 54)
    - Brown, Vinzarelli (Box A-18, Folder 55)
    - Brown, Viola Martin (Box A-18, Folder 56)
      Print has a staple in it.
    - Brown, Virpel (Box A-18, Folder 57)
    - Brown, Virginia A. (Box A-18, Folder 58)
    - Brown, Vivian (Box A-18, Folder 59)
    - Brown, Vivian H. (Box A-18, Folder 60)
      Photographer if identified: Elmo McDonald
    - Brown, Vivianne (Box A-18, Folder 61)
    - Brown, W.C. (Dr.) (Box A-18, Folder 62)
      Print has press release stapled to verso.
    - Brown, Walter (Major) (Box A-18, Folder 63)
    - Brown, Warden G. (Box A-18, Folder 64)
      Print has newspaper clipping glued to verso.
    - Brown, Warren (Box A-18, Folder 65)
    - Brown, Wayne (Box A-18, Folder 66)
    - Brown, Wes (Box A-18, Folder 67)
    - Brown, Wes (Box A-18, Folder 68)
    - Brown, Wesley A. (Box A-18, Folder 69)
      Photographer if identified: State University Construction Fund Photography
    - Brown, William (Box A-18, Folder 70)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Victor B. Greene
    - Brown, William (Box A-18, Folder 71)
      Photographer if identified: Photography by Wilson
    - Brown, William (Box A-18, Folder 72)
    - Brown, William (Bishop) (Box A-18, Folder 73)
      One print has blank leaf taped to verso.
    - Brown, William E. (Box A-18, Folder 74)
    - Brown, William H. III + wife (Box A-18, Folder 75)
    - Brown, William Harmon (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-18, Folder 76)
      One print has blank leaf glued to verso.
    - Brown, William (Mrs.) (Box A-18, Folder 77)
    - Brown, Willie (Box A-18, Folder 78)
    - Brown, Willie (Box A-18, Folder 79)
    - Brown, Willis (Box A-18, Folder 80)
    - Brown, Yvonne (Box A-18, Folder 81)
    - Brown, Z. Amgba (Box A-18, Folder 82)
    - Browne, Al (Box A-18, Folder 83)
    - Browne, Cheryl (Box A-18, Folder 84)
      Also one velox print and one halftone print.
    - Browne, Dora (Box A-18, Folder 85)
    - Browne, G. Stanley (Box A-18, Folder 86)
      Other print has press release attached with paperclip.
    - Browne, Ivan (Box A-18, Folder 87)
    - Browne, J. Zamgba (Box A-18, Folder 88)
    - Browne, James D. (Rev.) (Box A-18, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: Ulysses Allen Providence
    - Browne, Jocateria (Box A-18, Folder 90)
    - Browne, John L. (Box A-18, Folder 91)
    - Browne, Kenneth N. (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-18, Folder 92)
      One print housed in folder with typescript leaf attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Harold Stovall, Gill Photographers
    - Browne, Maxine (Box A-18, Folder 93)
    - Browne, Pearline (Mrs.) (Box A-18, Folder 94)
    - Browne, Robert (Box A-18, Folder 95)
    - Browne, Robert (Esq.) (Box A-18, Folder 96)
    - Browne, Robert S. (Box A-18, Folder 97)
      Photographer if identified: Harlem Prep. Photo Club
    - Browne, Roscoe (Dr.) (Box A-18, Folder 98)
      Note on folder: "President '100 Black Men.'"
    - Browne, Roscoe Lee (Box A-18, Folder 99)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, Friedman-Abeles
    - Browne, Tedd (Box A-18, Folder 100)
    - Brown, Tom (Box A-18, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: Del Brook Binns
    - Browne, Tom (entertainer) (Box A-18, Folder 102)
    - Browne, Yvonne (Box A-18, Folder 103)
    - Browner, Lorris (Box A-18, Folder 104)
    - Browning, Ivan (Box A-18, Folder 105)
    - Browning, Ivan H. (Box A-18, Folder 106)
    - Browning, M. Moss (Box A-18, Folder 107)
      Photographer if identified: Austin Studios
    - Brownsville (Box A-18, Folder 108)
    - Brownsville Community Council (Box A-18, Folder 109)